https://all4ed.org/privacy-policy/

Action Academy
The Alliance for Excellent Education’s Action Academy is an online learning community of education advocates. We invite you to create an account, expand your knowledge on the most pressing issues in education, and communicate with others...
Learn More
Register
Log in
Login with:
Username
Password
Remember me
Lost password?
Not an Action Academy Member yet? Register Now
ALLIANCE FOR EXCELLENT EDUCATION PRIVACY POLICY
The Alliance’s Commitment to Privacy
The Alliance for Excellent Education (the Alliance) is a national education policy, practice, and advocacy nonprofit organization. The Alliance values and respects the privacy of all visitors to www.all4ed.org and all other websites the Alliance maintains, including www.GraduationEffect.org, www.DeeperLearning4All.org, www.DigitalLearningDay.org, www.FutureReady.org, and www.PISADay.org (“Site(s)”). The Alliance only collects personal information from visitors that is necessary to provide the information and resources sought by visitors to the Site(s). This policy (“Privacy Policy” or “Policy”) explains the Alliance’s approach to the privacy of information that personally identifies each visitor (“the User”).
User Consent
Please read this Policy carefully. By using the Alliance’s Site(s), the User consents to the use and collection of personally identifying information in the manner described in this Policy. If the User does not agree to all the information contained in this Policy, the User should not use the Site(s) or other Alliance resources.
Changes to the Alliance’s Privacy Policy
Please check this Policy periodically for changes. The Alliance reserves the right to amend, update, remove, or revise its Privacy Policy at any time. If any changes are unacceptable to the User, the User may cease access to or use of the Site(s). If the User continues to access or use the Site(s) after changes are posted to the Privacy Policy, the User will be deemed to have accepted the changes. Information gathered now will be used in accordance with the Alliance’s Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. The Alliance expressly rejects any terms and conditions proposed by the User that are in addition to or conflict with the Privacy Policy.
The Alliance will make every effort to avoid drastic changes to this Policy unless necessary. However, to better serve its mission, the Alliance is continuously improving the way it operates. Therefore, it may be necessary for the Alliance to update or revise this Privacy Policy. If the Alliance makes material changes to this Policy with respect to how the User’s personal information is used or shared, the Alliance will first notify the User and give the User an opportunity to indicate consent to the new use or sharing of the User’s personally identifying information. The Alliance expressly rejects any terms and conditions proposed by the User that are in addition to or conflict with any changes to the Privacy Policy.
Information About the User
The Alliance collects, stores, and uses personal information the User voluntarily provides to the Alliance, including name, mailing address, and email address, to (1) communicate with the User; (2) help the User communicate with their elected or nonelected government representatives; (3) provide the User with relevant information and resources; and (4) improve the Alliance’s Site(s) and its services to the User.
If the User voluntarily submits personal information for inclusion on the Alliance’s e-list, it will collect the User’s demographic information and the User will receive the Alliance’s newsletter, as well as future communications about Alliance activities, services, or initiatives that it believes will be of interest to the User. The Alliance will do its best to respect the User’s time and attention. If the User has voluntarily provided identifying information to the Alliance, it may also collect usage information when the User visits the Alliance’s Site(s). The Alliance may also obtain information about the User from other sources and add it to the information already collected from the User. All information collected from the User’s use of the Alliance’s Site(s) or about the User from another source will be maintained and used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Why Certain Information Is Collected
The Alliance collects information to provide high-quality services and resources to better fulfill its mission and assist its users, including customizing users’ individual needs.
Sharing Personal Information
The Alliance will not sell, rent, or disclose the User’s email address or other personal information to any mass providers under any circumstance, or to a third party except an organization affiliated (“Affiliate”) with the Alliance, or to a third party the Alliance is partnering with on a specific project and under the condition that the User specifically authorizes the additional disclosure. Any initial communication from an Affiliate will provide the opportunity to opt out of obtaining subsequent communications from that organization.
When special projects may include sharing the User’s personal information with third parties, such as when the Alliance partners with another organization, it shall also be noted in the sign-up notification that the project may include sharing the User’s information and will provide an opt-in or opt-out mechanism.
Security
The Alliance realizes that the User may be concerned about the security of his/her personal information. Although the Alliance uses reasonable security measures to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information, no data transmission over the internet or wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secure. Therefore, the Alliance cannot guarantee the security of information the User transmits to the Alliance, and the User does so at his/her own risk. Electronic transmission of information and data is not necessarily secure against interception. Please be advised that the User should not send the Alliance or other entity information that contains personally identifying information unless it is required for a specific purpose. The Alliance will never request social security numbers, personally identifying numbers, health information, or other similar types of personal information. Additionally, the Alliance will never request banking or financial information with the limited exception of credit card information for individuals wishing to donate to the Alliance via the donate page.
Access
The User can remove themselves from our listing at here and the Alliance and they will no longer receive communications described in this Policy. Alternatively, the User can email Alliance@all4ed.org to request the deletion of or updates to his/her account.
Personal Information the User May Voluntarily Provide
The Alliance collects and maintains information voluntarily provided by visitors to its Site(s) or through other Alliance communication means. This information can include name, mailing address, email address, phone number, requested public comments, or other such information the User may voluntarily provide through various means on the Site(s), including subscribing to newsletters and blogs, participating in grassroots activities such as email groups, signing up for specific projects or initiatives, responding to surveys, signing a petition or letter, filling out a form, and other similar activities that allow the User to be contacted in furtherance of the activity. It is entirely up to the User to decide what, if any, voluntary personal information is provided.
Information the Alliance Collects Automatically
The Alliance automatically collects some information when a guest visits its Site(s). This includes information generated by the User’s web browser. This information may include the internet domain used to access the Site(s), internet protocol (IP) address of the computer being used, browser software and the operating system being used, date and time the User accessed the Site(s), and internet address used to link to the Alliance’s Site(s).
Use of Google Analytics and Cookies
Google Analytics are used to provide the Alliance with up-to-date user information from its Site(s) so it can provide high-quality services and information. This tool allows the Alliance to continually improve the Site(s). Google Analytics collects information such as how often the User visits the Site(s), services and pages visited and accessed on each visit, and other sites the User visits. Google Analytics collects the IP address of the computer used to access the Site(s), but it does not collect the User’s name or other identifying information nor is any effort made to identify the User with an IP address. Google Analytics collects this information through attachment of a permanent cookie upon visiting the Site(s) by the User. The User may prevent Google Analytics from recognizing him/her on a visit by disabling cookies on the browser being used. More information on Google Analytics privacy policies can be found at https://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html?hl=en-GB.
Retention of Personal Information
The Alliance reserves the right to retain personal or other information collected on the Site(s) or through other communication means in accordance with this Privacy Policy for as long as it may be necessary to maintain it.
Links to Third-Party Websites
The Alliance’s Site(s) and/or other Alliance resources may contain links to third-party websites when they are relevant to activities or issues of interest to its users or that further its mission. The Alliance is not responsible for the privacy practices, policies, or content of third-party sites. If the User links to a third-party website, he/she is subject to the terms of service and privacy policy of that individual site and the Alliance’s Privacy Policy will not apply to any activity by the User on that third-party link. Clicking on a third-party website is a voluntary action and strictly up to the User. The User is encouraged to review the individual privacy policies of all website the User visits.
Choice
The User can always choose not to provide the Alliance with personal information, although it may be needed to access or receive certain information, such as the Alliance’s newsletter. If the User provides the Alliance with personal information, he/she may elect not to be contacted by the Alliance by indicating as such when creating or updating the User’s records with the Alliance.
Alliance Site(s) Are Not Intended for Children
Since the Alliance has no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access the Alliance’s Site(s) unless it receives a specific notification, the Alliance implements the same Privacy Policy for the Sites’ users of all ages. However, while the Alliance is a nonprofit organization dedicated to improving K–12 education, its Site(s) are NOT directed at individuals under 13 years of age nor does the Alliance intend to collect personally identifying information from those under 13 years of age. By using the Alliance’s Site(s), the User represents and warrants that he/she is at least 18 years of age or older. If a child has provided the Alliance with personally identifying information without the consent of a parent or guardian, the parent or guardian should immediately contact the Alliance to remove the information from its records.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) Compliance
The Alliance operates its Site(s) and complies with all legal requirements under 15 USC §§ 6501-6506: the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). Accordingly, the Alliance does not knowingly collect personally identifying data or other information from children under the age of 13. Parents and legal guardians are encouraged to monitor their children’s computer and internet activity. Children under 18 years of age should be instructed to never provide information on the Alliance’s Site(s). If a child has provided the Alliance with personally identifying information without the consent of a parent or guardian, the parent or guardian should contact the Alliance immediately to remove the information from the Alliance’s records. More information on COPPA can be found at http://www.coppa.org/comply.htm.
Age Disclaimer: The Alliance for Excellent Education’s Site(s) and all data-collection tools associated with them are not intended for use by children under the age of 18. By using these Site(s), the User represents and warrants to the Alliance that he/she is at least age 18 years of age or older.
Contact the Alliance
If the User has concerns about their privacy at the Alliance’s Site(s), or when using other Alliance resources, or the User does not wish to be contacted by the Alliance in the future, please email alliance@all4ed.org.
Recent Activity
topratedforbaby earned badge
Early Bird
lward attended webinar
When Equity Is Optional: ESSA’s Fifth Anniversary and Early Lessons from...
(+5 pts)
khartley attended webinar
Test
(+5 pts)
khartley attended webinar
When Equity Is Optional: ESSA’s Fifth Anniversary and Early Lessons from...
(+5 pts)
(5.00)
Video
"Federal Flash 9/16/16: House Passes CTE; Alexander Encourages Lawsuits"
Rating
(5.00)
Video
"Federal Flash: February 5: News on the Every Student Succeeds Act; New...
Rating
(5.00)
Video
"Federal Flash: January 15: What's Next for NCLB Rewrite?"
Rating
(5.00)
Video
"Federal Flash: January 29: ESSA Timelines and Implementation"
Rating
(5.00)
Every Child a Graduate. Every Child Prepared for Life.
